[music]
>> Hi, I'm Samuel, creator of Pydantic here
at PyCon US this year. Come talk to me
about anything Pydantic, particularly
Pydantic Monty, and in particular come
along tomorrow at 11:00 to 201B to hear
me talk about whatever I'm going to talk
about. I better figure that out between
now and then.
Hi everyone. My name is Laís. I'm super
excited to be here at PyCon US [music]
2026 in Long Beach.
I look after dev rel and growth
marketing for Pydantic, [music] and you
should come
talk to us about everything Pydantic.
Hey everyone, this is Jameson from
Pydantic. I'm a technical account
executive, and I'm looking forward to
talking to you about Logfire, tracing,
and making your agents better.
Hey, I'm Marcelo. I work at Pydantic. I
do back-end engineering work.
I'm here at PyCon US in Long Beach, and
I'm happy to talk about Pydantic AI
Gateway and other stuff that Pydantic is
building.
Hi everyone, I'm Adrian. I'm one of the
founding engineers at Pydantic. I'm
[music] really excited to be here at
PyCon. Come talk to me about data
infrastructure, querying, or analytical
use cases.